bsaving.com 2014-04-20

# bSaving

The following sets forth the policies for the collection and use of personally identifiable information ("Information") by bSaving.com (together with its parent and affiliated companies, in connection with its operation of the Web site located at bSaving.com (the "bSaving" or "Site").

**_Collection of Information_**. In connection with the Site, bSaving may collect Information in the following ways: 

  * Through registration forms and surveys filled out by a user on the Site
  * Through Information provided by a user in connection with the purchase of products or services on the Site
  * Through the maintenance and analysis of Web server logs
  * Via e-mail sent by a user to bSaving
  * Through the use by bSaving of third-party databases from which user Information is extracted and combined with Information obtained by bSaving through other means.

bSaving may also connect non-personally identifiable information from users via "cookies" (small text files placed by bSaving on user computers), single-pixel GIF image files (also called "Web beacons"), Web server log analysis and other similar technological means. Such non-personally identifiable information may be used to track site trends and enhance the user experience, and may be shared with third parties. To the extent third parties may place advertising on the Site, such third parties may utilize cookies or other technological means within the advertising to collect and utilize non-personally identifiable information. bSaving is not responsible for information collected by third parties in this manner, nor for the collection or use of Information by other sites to which the Site is linked. 

**_Types of Information Collected by bSaving_**. The following types of Information about a user are among those that may be collected by bSaving in connection with the Site: 

  * Name
  * Postal address
  * E-mail address
  * Telephone number
  * Cellular telephone number
  * Facsimile number
  * Date of birth
  * Age
  * Gender
  * Other demographic information (e.g. occupation, income range)
  * IP Address
  * Referring site
  * Other technical information collected by the Site's servers.

**_No Collection of Information from Children_**. The Site is not intended for users under the age of 18, nor does bSaving knowingly collect or retain Information in connection with the Site from children under the age of 13. 

**_Use of Information_**. bSaving may use Information collected in connection with the Site in the following ways: 

  * To provide requested information, survey results, products and services to users
  * To improve the user experience with the Site
  * In connection with the operation of the Site and bSaving's internal business
  * In connection with other Sites or offline businesses owned or operated by bSaving
  * For Users to obtain information and offers for products and services offered by bSaving as well as selected third parties.

In order to do the foregoing, bSaving may provide your Information to third parties, including but not limited to third party marketers and vendors as well as third party contractors providing services to bSaving for the operation of the Site and its business, communication services and fulfillment of orders. bSaving will use commercially reasonable efforts to limit use of the Information by such third parties to the specific uses set forth above. bSaving also utilizes electronic and physical security to reduce the risk of improper access to or manipulation of Information during transmission and storage, but cannot guarantee the security or integrity of the Information. bSaving may also disclose Information when it determines it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or regulations or protect the interests or safety of bSaving, its customers, or other visitors to the Site. 

**_Access to Information_**. Users may modify and correct certain Information through a written request sent to customerservice@bsaving.com 

**_Changes to this Privacy Policy_**. bSaving reserves the right to revise and update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such revisions will be effective on the date of posting to the Site, and will apply to all information collected by bSaving both prior to and following the effective date. Your use of the Site following any such revisions will be deemed your acceptance of such revisions. Users should periodically visit this page to review the current policies with regard to Information. 

**_Opting Out From Offers From bSaving_**. At any time, a user may opt out from receiving future offers from bSaving by following the instructions contained within each marketing communication. Such opting out will not apply to any communications from third parties to whom bSaving may have provided Information regarding the user. Third parties' use of the Information is subject to such parties' own privacy policies, for which bSaving shall not be responsible. 

**_Your California Privacy Rights_**. Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of bSaving who are California residents to request certain information regarding bSaving's disclosure of personal information for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to: 2200 SW 10th Street, Deerfield Beach, FL 33442. Within thirty days of receiving such a request, bSaving will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. bSaving reserves its right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this paragraph.

2200 SW 10th St   
Deerfield Beach, FL 33442   
954.312.4700  

Policy Last Revised: November 23, 2011
